Hey! I got you a present!
Oh, my goodness,
where did you hide it?
I got it for your wedding
and I ordered it weeks ago
and it finally got here.
You didn't have
to get us anything.
You already did so...
I love it! It's huge!
Let's open it!
Open it!
It's a Ms. Pac-Man machine!
Oh, my God!
I didn't know
where to put it
so I left it
here for now.
Maybe we can put it
in the guest bedroom.
Yeah, okay.
I kind of like it here.
So do you really like it?
Are you kidding?
I practically spent
my entire childhood
at the arcade.
This is like...
oh, my God.
This is like
my second-favorite game.
Oh, really,
what was your first?
Well, I don't really remember
the name of it.
Well, what'd it do?
Well, just... you put
a quarter in and, you know
pull some handles and you win
like, a candy bar or something.
A vending machine?
Hey, don't feel bad for me.
I won every time.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey.
I'm so glad you
guys are here.
I've been dying to tell someone
what happened
in the Paleontology department
today.
You think he saw us or
can we still slip out?
Professor Newman, the head of
the department is retiring so...
They made you head
of the department.
No, I get to teach
one of his advanced classes.
Why didn't I get
head of the department?
Oh, hey, Rach, listen,
I got a big date coming up.
Do you know of
a good restaurant?
Uh, Paul's Cafe.
It's got great food and
it's really romantic.
Ooh, great, thanks.
Ooh, and then afterwards
you could take her
to the Four Seasons
for drinks.
Or go downtown and
listen to some jazz.
Or dancing.
Oh, take her dancing.
You sure are naming
a lot of ways
to postpone sex,
I'll tell you.
Oh, I miss dating.
Getting all dressed
up, going to a fancy
restaurant.
I'm not going to be able
to do that for so long.
And it's so much fun.
I mean, not that
sitting at home
worrying about
giving birth
to a 16-pound baby
is not fun.
Hey, you know what?
Why don't I take you out.
Joey, you don't want
to go on a date with
a pregnant lady.
Yes, I do.
And we're going to go out
we're going to have
a good time.
I'm going to take your
mind off of childbirth
and C-sections and...
and giant baby heads
stretching out...
Okay, okay, I'll go
with you, I'll go.
I'll go with you.
It'd be fun.
All right?
No, no. Yes!
Ah.
Oh, would you look
at that, Monica.
I just knocked off
all your top scores.
How sad.
Okay, I'm next.
Don't start another game.
I said I was next.
Phoebe.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I couldn't hear you
over all the winning.
Chandler,
Phoebe's hogging the game.
Who cares?
It's a stupid game.
You only think it's stupid
because you suck at it.
I don't suck. It sucks.
You suck.
Wait, okay, if this game
is going to cause problems
between the two of you
then maybe
I should just keep it.
No, no, no.
No, I love it.
It is a great present.
In fact, why
don't you go home
and wait for
the thank-you card.
Why do you want to play
so badly?
Yeah, it's not like it
spits out a Clark bar
after every game.
Okay, Phoebe, that's it,
get out of the chair.
Come on, out of the chair.
Oh! Phoebe...
( knocking on door )
Joey, could you get that?
What are you doing here?
I thought you were in your room.
No, I'm picking you
up for our date.
These are for you.
Oh... Lilies.
Joey, they're my favorite.
Thank you.
And...
a brownie.
( gasps )
Well, half a brownie.
Actually, it's just the bag.
It was a long walk
from the flower shop
and I was starting
to feel faint, so...
Oh, man.
This is so great.
I actually feel like
I'm going on a real date.
Although I have a hint
of morning sickness
and I'm wearing
underwear that goes up
to about... ( snaps ) there.
Hey, come on now,
this is a real date.
So, nice place you got here.
Foosball, huh.
Pizza box.
Oh, a subscription to Playboy.
My kind of woman.
Yeah, actually,
that's my roommate's.
I would like to meet him.
He sounds like a standup guy.
Ah, yes, but he's
very protective of me
so you better
watch yourself.
Hey, so this roommate of yours,
is he good-looking?
Mm-hmm.
It must be tough to keep
your hands off him, huh?
( chuckles )
Yeah, but I'm pretty sure
he's gay.
No, no, no, he's not.
No, why are you trying
to ruin the game?
Come on.
( chuckling )
...which brings us
back, of course
to Greeley's theory
of dominance.
Okay, that's it
for today.
Oh, uh, does anyone know
where the Freeman Building is?
Yeah, it's the new building
on Avenue "A."
What?
That's all the way across town.
I'm supposed to teach a graduate
seminar there in ten minutes.
Ooh, dude,
that's not going to happen.
Move it, move it!
Move it!
Hey! I'm the teacher!
( panting )
( wheezing )
Hello.
( panting )
I'm sorry I'm a little late.
Uh, whoa, a lot late.
Well, let me start by, uh...
by introducing myself.
I'm Professor Geller.
( bell rings )
So, to sum up...
I'm Professor Geller.
Good job today.
Now the filet mignon,
what comes with that?
There's a side
of steamed vegetables.
Mm...
Now instead of the vegetables
is there any way
that I could substitute
the, um... three-pound lobster?
You know what,
bring her both.
And I'll have the same.
Wow, this is shaping up
to be a pretty good date.
Oh, I almost forgot,
I didn't pay you
the rent check.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
no roommate stuff, okay?
We're on a date.
Okay.
Wow, so I get to see
what Joey Tribbiani
is like on a date.
So do you have any moves?
No... no, I'm just myself.
And if they
don't like me for...
( laughs )
I'm sorry, I couldn't
even get through that.
( laughing )
I knew it, I knew it.
Come on, tell me
your moves.
All right, um...
well, okay, I usually start
by having a bottle of wine
sent to my table
from a fan.
Oh, my God.
And that works?
Well, it does when you
combine it with
"This is so embarrassing.
I just want to have
a normal life."
Oh, you poor little
famous man.
Oh, okay,
how about this one:
I was going to
wait until the end of
the night to kiss you
but you're just
so beautiful...
I don't think I can.
Oh, my God.
That was fantastic.
I almost leaned in.
I really almost did.
All right, so tell me
one of your moves.
All right...
( clears throat )
So where'd you grow up?
That's your move?
Boy, Rach, you're
lucky you're hot.
Come on, just answer
the question.
Queens.
And so were you close
to your parents?
Yeah, with my mom, yeah.
Not so much with my dad.
Why not?
I don't know.
I guess there's just always
been this distance, you know.
I mean, we both try
to pretend it's not there
but... but it is.
( sighs )
That's got to be rough.
It is, yeah,
it's really tough.
You know sometimes
I think...
Wow.
Nice move.
Uh-huh.
"Where'd you grow up?"
So simple.
Thank you.
Now if you'll excuse me
I'm going to go
to the restroom.
And now you're
watching me walk away.
Yes, I am.
Again, so simple.
Hey.
You are not going to believe
what I did today.
Well, it clearly wasn't
showering or shaving.
I got good.
I played this game all day
and now I rule at it.
They should change the name
of it to Ms. Chandler.
Although I hope they don't.
Wait a minute.
You stayed home all day
and played Ms. Pac-Man
while I went off to work
like some kind of chump?
Uh-huh, and I got
all the top ten scores.
I erased Phoebe off the board.
High five.
What is the matter
with your hand?
Well, I've been playing it
for like, eight hours.
It'll loosen up.
Come on, check out
the scores.
And also look
at the initials.
They're dirty words.
Chandler, why would you do that?
Because it's awesome.
You think this is clever?
Well, they only give you
three letters
so after A-S-S,
it is a bit of a challenge.
Wait a minute,
this one's not dirty.
Well, it is when you put it
together with that one.
Oh.
Well, if you don't
clear this off
you won't be getting
one of those from me.
Ben's coming over tomorrow
to play this game.
This can't be there.
Come on, he won't even
know what they mean.
Chandler, he's seven,
he's not stupid.
Have you talked to him lately?
All right, look,
I'm just going
to unplug it...
No, no, no
if you unplug it I'll have
nothing to show for my day.
It'll be like I was at work.
No.
Hey, look at that.
Look at that,
it's still there.
This thing must have
some kind of primitive
wrong chip in it
or something.
Honey, you got
to beat your scores.
With the claw?
All right, fine.
Fine, I'll do it.
Just got to get this
off the screen.
Carol and Susan are still upset
that you taught him
"Pull My Finger."
Pull my finger.
My hand is messed up.
I am not going to answer that.
Oh, come on,
just pick one.
Between Monica, Phoebe,
Chandler and Ross
if you had to--
who would you punch?
No one. They are my friends.
I wouldn't punch any of them.
Chandler?
Yeah, but I don't know why.
We're having
such a wonderful time.
Me, too.
Hey, Rach,
can I just say
I think this is the
best date I ever had.
I know.
I've never laughed
so hard that...
Did you see the wine
come out of my nose?
Yes. Joey,
I think everybody
saw the wine
come out of your nose.
Yeah. I got to say
I never knew
I could enjoy
the non-sex part
of a date so much.
Well, that is because
you have never been
on a date with me before.
Oh.
Huh.
All right, now don't judge me.
I normally wait till my date
leaves, but you live here.
I'm ripping into this one.
Okay, well, then,
you don't judge me.
I'm going to suck
on the cellophane
from the brownie I had before.
Mm. Mmm.
So tell me--
What are Joey Tribbiani's
end-of-the-night moves?
Uh...
Well.
If I want the girl to kiss me
the first thing I do
is make my lips
look irresistible.
How do you do that?
You can't tell anyone,
but, uh...
I put on a shiny lip balm.
Oh, my God.
Yeah. Like a moth to a flame,
I'm telling you.
Okay, all right,
so... now you go.
No, I don't want to tell you.
Why not?
'Cause it's embarrassing.
More embarrassing
than shiny raspberry lip balm?
I didn't say "raspberry"
before, did I?
Just tell me, Rach--
just tell me.
Okay.
All right. Stand up.
Well, when we're
at the door...
I lightly press my
lips against his
and then move into his
body, just for a second
and then I make
this sound...
( low moan )
Okay, I know
it doesn't sound
like anything
but I swear--
it works.
Yo, ah, well,
that would work, yeah.
All right, I got
to go to bed.
I had such a wonderful time.
Yeah.
Me, too.
You were 50 minutes
late to the class?
What, did you crawl there?
No, I ran, okay?
It's really far
and when did people stop
understanding the phrase
"Get the hell out of my way"?
Well, why didn't you
just take a cab?
Between the traffic
that time of day
and all the one-way streets,
it would take me twice as long.
Besides, I teach the class
three times a week.
Who am I, Rockefeller?
Well, you're not going
to be able to keep doing this.
Well, I have to, okay?
If I don't, they'll take
the class away from me
and I already put it
in my family newsletter.
Your what?
You've seen it--
the Geller Yeller.
Right.
Wow.
Besides, I think I figured out
a much faster route.
I'm sure I can
make it this time.
I just, just can't be afraid
to get a little bit...
hit by cars.
Hey.
Hi. Hey.
Remember last night how
we were talking
about that movie Cujo?
Oh, yeah. I still
can't believe
you haven't seen Cujo.
What is wrong with you?
Relax. It's not like
it's Citizen Kane.
Have you ever tried to
sit through Citizen Kane?
Yeah, I know,
it's really boring
but it's like a big deal.
Yeah.
Anyway...
I was thinking
about renting
Cujo sometime.
Oh, yeah. All right.
Well, let's do it tonight.
Well, don't you have
that big date tonight?
Oh, right.
Hey, Joey, can I
ask you something?
Yeah.
After our date last night
did you feel a little weird?
Oh, my God, you did, too?
It totally freaked me out.
What was that?
I don't know.
I'm-I'm kind of thinking
it was the lobster.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
The lobster.
Yeah, I was up sick all night.
Yeah, me, too. All night.
Really?
How come we didn't cross paths?
Yeah, well, that's
because, uh...
I stayed in my room.
Yeah, you don't want
to look in my hamper.
Okay, I got that.
I'll escape over there
and back over here...
All right, come on,
Ms. Pac-Man.
It's got right...
( "game over" tones )
Well, you're just a little
bitch, aren't you?
Hey, you guys?
Listen, I'm sorry
that I was hogging
the game before.
Oh, my God.
Your friends have some
unfortunate initials.
They're all Chandler.
Chandler sucks.
He couldn't have
gotten this good.
I did, but it came at a price.
Well, Ben's coming over tonight
and he can't see this.
Come on, by
age seven
kids have already
seen orgies.
Was it just me?
( gasping for air )
( growling )
Ah, yes, I made it.
I'm on time.
Okay.
Why don't we all, uh...
( gasps )
...open our books
to page 23, where...
( gasps )
where you will see a, uh...
...a bunch of red spots.
Okay, why don't you all
start to read while I...?
Hey.
Are you all right?
You seem a little distracted.
No, no. I'm fine.
It's just... Hey.
Can I ask you something?
Have you ever looked at someone
that you've known for a while...
and, and suddenly... suddenly
seen them in a different way?
You mean, like from behind?
Yeah. Yeah,
that's exactly it. Yeah.
You know what? One time
I saw this guy from behind
and he seemed
like a totally normal guy
and then you turned around
and it was Stephen Baldwin.
Whoo. Yeah.
So, yeah. So you know
exactly what I'm talking about.
Totally.
Wow.
Would you excuse me for a sec?
Sure.
Eh.
Oh, my God, Phoebe,
you're on fire.
I know.
One more score to go.
You can do it.
Don't touch me!
Don't touch her!
All right, go
left. Go left.
Go right! Go right!
I can't! I can't!
( "game over" tones )
No! You son of a b...!
( opera music playing )
Phoebe!
Oh. Hi, Ben.
No, don't look at the machine.
( door opens )
( shrieks )
God! Thank God
you're home.
I'm watching Cujo.
Alone?
Yes.
Well, what is wrong
with this dog?
Hey, did you
get to the part
where they're trapped in
the car and Cujo's
throwing himself
at the windshield?
No. No, seriously,
what's wrong with the dog?
Wait a minute-- what are you
doing home so early?
What happened to your date?
Oh, uh... didn't work out.
Well, you
want to watch
the rest
of the movie with me?
Oh, uh... okay. Yeah.
You know, I never thought
I would ever
say this about a movie
but I really hope this dog dies.
What are you
doing over there?
Come sit here. You protect me.
Oh, sure. Yeah. Why not?
Okay.
Okay, that's him,
that's him.
That's Cujo,
that's Cujo.
All right, all right,
I know, I know.
It's going to be okay.
Oh, my God...
What's he going
to do now?
I can't watch!
( whimpering )
Oh... seriously, how
can you watch this?
Aren't you scared?
Terrified.
So, is everybody here?
I got here
a little early, myself.
Let us begin.
Now, the hadrosaurids
have been unearthed
in two main locations...
Here.
And...
here.
Now, as for the hydrosaurs...
( wood cracking )
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org